<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_intro_page SYSTEM "software_intro.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY development_team SYSTEM "development_team.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY development_join SYSTEM "development_join.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY translations SYSTEM "translation.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="development_help">
<config param="desc" value="Help us"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
<title>Help us</title>
<summary>Direct and indirect support for the development of BibleTime</summary>
<keywords>BibleTime, Help us, Help BibleTime, Software</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Please help us ...</title>
<para>
Our aim is to develop BibleTime into a really mature Bible study application that 
can by everyone. To ahieve this, we need your help. There are different possibilities
for supporting the BibleTime project directly and indirectly:
</para>

<section><title>Do you want to pray?</title>
<para>
Praying is something everybody can do. If you are praying for the Sword and BibleTime projects you are helping us as much as the other team members of the BibleTime project.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>Would you like to support the developers?</title>
<para>
On the <olink targetdocent="development_team">team page</olink>, you can find information about 
the members of the BibleTime team and ways how you can support them. If you like using BibleTime, 
but don't have the time or knowledge to help with the development yourself, you might want to consider 
this possibility.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>Do you know how to program software?</title>
<para>
Do you know how to program in C++? Are you familiar with the KDE programming 
interface or are motivate to learn it? If you have time to regularly work 
on the BibleTime source code we ask you to join our team.
If you want to do so, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join">
Join us</olink>.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>Do you know how to write documentation?</title>
<para>
Do you think you would be good in working on BibleTime's english documentation?
If you think you are, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join">
Join us</olink>.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>Are you good in translating english into another language?</title>
<para>
BibleTime should be useable for everyone. That's why we need a translation into your language, 
if it's not yet available. If you decide to start working on a translation please contact us 
at info@bibletime.info to see whether the translation was not yet started by another team 
member. We will provide you with the files which should be translated.
</para>
<para>
You can find more information about the translation process on the page <olink targetdocent="translations">
translation</olink>.
</para>
</section>
</section>

</webpage>
