<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../en/schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_about SYSTEM "software_about.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY software_download SYSTEM "software_download.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY documentation_requirements SYSTEM "documentation_requirements.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY documentation_installation_modules SYSTEM "documentation_installation_modules.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY documentation_faq SYSTEM "documentation_faq.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="documentation_installation_bibletime">
<config param="desc" value="Installation of the BibleTime software"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
<title>BibleTime</title>
<summary>Introduction to the BibleTime software</summary>
<keywords>BibleTime, Software, Installation, Help, Sword, Download</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Installation of BibleTime</title>
<para>
This page explains how BibleTime should be installed. Please follow these steps to get a working installation of BibleTime quickly.
</para>

<section><title>The two ways to install BibleTime</title>
	<para>
	There are two possibilities to install BibleTime on your system:
		<orderedlist>
			<listitem>Install using prebuilt binary packages, like RPM or DEB</listitem>
			<listitem>Compile BibleTime from sources on your own system</listitem>
		</orderedlist>
	</para>

	<para>
	We recommend the installation using the binary packages. It's the simplest way.
	</para>
</section>

<section><title>Prebuilt binary packages</title>
	<para>
	We try to provide packages for the most important Linux distributions. These include RedHat, Mandrake and SuSE.
	</para>

	<para>
	First download the binary package for your Linux distribution. For example:
	You want to download BibleTime 1.2.2 for SuSE Linux 8.1. In this case you have to download the package "bibletime-1.2.2-1suse8.1.i586.rpm".

	Please don't forgot to download the package bibletime-i18n to get the documentation and the translations, which are available for BibleTime.
	</para>

	<para>
	As you can see each package name contains the Linux distribution and version is was built for. Please don't try to install a package on another system as it was built for.
	</para>

	<para>
	You can download BibleTime here: <olink targetdocent="software_download">Download BibleTime</olink>.
	Don't forget to install some text modules after you installed BibleTime: <olink targetdocent="documentation_installation_modules">How to install the text modules</olink>.
	</para>
</section>


<section><title>Compilation from source code</title>
	<para>
	Installation using BibleTime's source code is more difficult than using binary packages. Please follow the steps below if you decided to install BibleTime from sources:

	<orderedlist>
		<listitem>
			Install the required software: <olink targetdocent="documentation_requirements">BibleTime's requirements</olink>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			Get the source code package of BibeTime: <olink targetdocent="software_download">Download</olink>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			Compile and install BibleTime:
			<programlisting>
<![CDATA[
	./configure --prefix=<your KDE directory>
	make
 	make install
]]>
			</programlisting>
			You can get your KDE directory by running the command  <command>kde-config --prefix</command>.
			If you get problems please read the <olink targetdocent="documentation_faq">FAQ</olink>.
			If there's no solution of your problem, please contact us at <email>info@bibletime.info</email>
		</listitem>
	</orderedlist>

	Don't forget to install some text modules after you installed BibleTime: <olink targetdocent="documentation_installation_modules">How to install the text modules</olink>.
	</para>
</section>

</section>
</webpage>
