<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_about SYSTEM "software_about.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="software">
<config param="desc" value="Software page"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
	<title>Software</title>
	<summary>Welcome to BibleTime</summary>
	<keywords>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, webpage</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Welcome to the BibleTime project.</title>
<para>
BibleTime is a Bible study application for Linux.
It is based on the <ulink url="http://www.kde.org/">K Desktop Environment</ulink> and
uses the <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/">Sword</ulink>
programming library to work with Bible texts, commentaries, dictionaries and books
provided by the <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/">Crosswire Bible Society</ulink>.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>News about BibleTime</title>
	
	<formalpara><title>2005-07-16: BibleTime 1.5</title>
		<para>BibleTime 1.5 is available now. It contains many new features and improvements.
			The source code of BibleTime 1.5 and Sword 1.5.8 is available in the download section. We hope to provide binary and translation packages for the most important Linux distributions in the next few weeks.
		</para>
		<para>Please use our new forums to discuss about this new release. Translators are encouraged to update their translations.</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2005-06-17: BibleTime 1.5 release candidate 2</title>
		<para>
			The second release candidate of BibleTime version 1.5 was released today.  It contains fixes for most of the problems found in 1.5rc1 and some more additional improvements.
			Please report all problems and bugs you encounter <ulink url="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=521207&amp;group_id=954&amp;func=browse">here</ulink>. The source code of BibleTime 1.5rc2 and Sword 1.5.8 is available in the download section.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2005-06-15: BibleTime forums online</title>
		<para>
			In the ongoing effort to build a BibleTime user community the BibleTime forums are now available for everybody at <ulink url="http://forum.bibletime.info/">forum.bibletime.info</ulink>. All users of BibleTime are encouraged to use these forums to discuss everything related to BibleTime.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2005-05-29: BibleTime 1.5 release candidate 1</title>
		<para>
			The first release candidate of BibleTime version 1.5 was released today. It contains a ton of fixes, improvements and new features. Everybody who is capable to install software using the source code is encouraged to test this release. Please report all problems and bugs you encounter <ulink url="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=521207&amp;group_id=954&amp;func=browse">here</ulink>. The source code of BibleTime 1.5rc1 and Sword 1.5.8 is available in the download section.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2005-01-24: Bible software Survey</title>
		<para>
		Bible Software vendors from around the globe are jointly sponsoring a cooperative User Survey to glean from Bible Software Users worldwide their needs, requests, and dreams.
		We'd be glad if you could take the survey here:
		<ulink url="http://www.surveymonkey.com/s.asp?u=91866814127">Bible software survey</ulink>
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2004-12-23: Status update</title>
		<para>
		The BibleTime project is still alive and development is almost finished for the next version, BibleTime 1.5. This version will contain major user interface improvements which will make it simpler to use than any other version before. We hope to release version 1.5 in the first three months of the next year.
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2004-05-25: Documentation author(s) needed</title>
		<para>
		The BibleTime team is in urgent need of one or more volunteers who want to work on the documentation. The handbook is outdated and needs a major update before the next version of BibleTime can be released. If you have some free time and know how to work with docbook files (or are ready to learn it), plase contact us at <email>info@bibletime.info</email>.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2004-02-09: BibleTime 1.4.1 for Mac OS X</title>
		<para>
		On the BibleTime development list <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/pipermail/bt-devel/2004-February/005181.html">Daniel Glassey writes</ulink> that BibleTime is now available for Mac OSX. To get BibleTime running on Mac please follow the instructions in <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/pipermail/bt-devel/2004-February/005163.html">this eMail</ulink> and <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/pipermail/bt-devel/2004-February/005181.html">this eMail</ulink>. Please report problems or success to <email>info@bibletime.info</email>.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2004-01-29: BibleTime 1.4.1</title>
		<para>
		BibleTime 1.4.1 was released today. The most important changes in version 1.4.1 are updated translations and bugfixes, especially in the Sword setup dialog.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2004-01-26: User forums online</title>
		<para>
		We're happy to announce a forum for BibleTime users. Please ask all your questions there if you need help. We'd appreciate all feedback and suggestions in the forum, too. The address is <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/forums">http://www.crosswire.org/forums</ulink>.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
	
	<formalpara><title>2004-01-16: Debian packages available</title>
		<para>
		<ulink url="http://packages.debian.org/unstable/kde/bibletime">Debian packages of BibleTime 1.4</ulink> are available now in Debian Unstable. Be sure to get the <ulink url="http://packages.debian.org/unstable/kde/bibletime-i18n">bibletime-i18n package</ulink>, too. Kudos to our Debian packager Daniel Glassey for his work!
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2004-01-11: New translation effort</title>
		<para>
		First of all we want to wish all of you a truly happy and blessed new year.
		</para>
		<para>
		As you probably already noticed, there is a new page online called
		<ulink url="translation.shtml">&quot;Translation&quot;</ulink>. This page gives an introduction into how you can help with the translation of the different areas of the BibleTime project,
		and offers detailed statistics on the completeness of the existing languages. Be sure to check it out.
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2003-12-29: BibleTime 1.4</title>
		<para>
		The new version 1.4 of BibleTime is now available for download. 1.4 in comparision with version 1.3 contains a new SwordSetup dialog to setup Sword and to install modules from local sources or from the internet. With the SwordSetup part it's also possible to remove modules from disk. 1.4 also contains many new bugfixes.
BibleTime 1.4 is available on our download page.		</para>
		<para>
		You need Sword 1.5.7 with enabled curl support to make use of the remote installation features. The binary packages we provide for some of the major linux distributions should work out of the box.
		</para>
		<para>
		If you run into troubles installing BibleTime or you have problems using it please submit a bugreport. We need your support to improve BibleTime.
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2003-12-03: BibleTime 1.4beta1</title>
		<para>
		The first testing version of the upcoming BibleTime 1.4 was released today.
		The new feature in comparision with 1.3 is the new SwordSetup dialog which makes
		the Sword and module configuration more userfriendly.
		Using the dialog you can now setup Sword's configuration files, install modules from
		the internet or from local sources (e.g. a CD) and also uninstall modules from your system.
		This beta release also contains some important bugfixes.
		</para>
		<para>
		This 1.4beta1 release is only meant for testing, so we do not provide binary packages.
		If you know how to compile programs from source code we encourage you to try this beta1 release.
		You need Sword 1.5.6 with enabled curl support to make use of the remote installation features.
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2003-10-19: SuSE 9.0 packages</title>
		<para>
		RPM packages are now available for SuSE 9.0. Report any problems to info@bibletime.info. Thank you!
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2003-10-16: New webpages</title>
		<para>
		BibleTime has now new webpages which offer better navigation, better design and
		faster page download time.
		</para>
		<para>
		If you experience any problems with the new pages please let us know!
		</para>
	</formalpara>

	<formalpara><title>2003-08-23: BibleTime 1.3</title>
		<para>
		Version 1.3 of BibleTime is finally available. BibleTime 1.3 contains a lot of new features, usability improvements and bug fixes. Upgrading to version 1.3 is strongly recommended for all our users.
		You can get the Software here: <ulink url="http://www.bibletime.info/software/download/">Download</ulink>.
		Binary packages will be released in the next few days.
		</para>
		<para>
 		Get the bibletime and the bibletime-i18n packages for full functionality.
 		We're very sorry for the long release time, we hope to shorten it with the next releases.
		</para>
	</formalpara>
</section>

</webpage>
