<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_about SYSTEM "software_about.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY software_faq SYSTEM "software_faq.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="documentation_installation_bibletime">
<config param="desc" value="Installation of the BibleTime software"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
<title>Download</title>
<summary>Installation to the BibleTime software</summary>
<keywords>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, installation</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Download BibleTime</title>
<para>
	This is a short list of available download locations. Packages which are not provided on our SourceForge pages might be outdated. Please see below for detailed download and installation instructions.
	<itemizedlist>
		<listitem>
		<para>Sourcecode and packages for major Linux distributions can be downloaded from <ulink url="http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=954">SourceForge</ulink>.
		</para>
		</listitem>

		<listitem>
		<para>Debian packages are available for <ulink url="http://packages.debian.org/unstable/kde/bibletime">Debian Unstable</ulink> and <ulink url="http://packages.debian.org/stable/x11/bibletime">Debian Stable</ulink>.
		</para>
		</listitem>

		<listitem>
		<para>Gentoo packages are available on <ulink url="http://packages.gentoo.org/search/?sstring=bibletime">www.gentoo.org</ulink>.
		</para>
		</listitem>

		<listitem>
		<para>A FreeBSD application port of BibleTime can be found on <ulink url="http://www.FreeBSD.org/cgi/ports.cgi?query=bibletime&amp;stype=all">www.freebsd.org</ulink>.
		</para>
		</listitem>

	</itemizedlist>
</para>
</section>

<section><title>Installation of BibleTime</title>
<para>
This section explains how to install BibleTime on your system. Basically there are two ways to install it: Either by using prebuilt binary packages or by compiling from source code. Installing BibleTime using prebuilt packages is the easiest way.
</para>

	<section><title>Prebuilt binary packages</title>
		<para>We try to provide packages for the most important Linux distributions. These include RedHat, Mandrake and SuSE.
		</para>

		<para>First download the binary package for your Linux distribution. For example: You want to download <application>BibleTime 1.4</application> for <productname>SuSE Linux 9.0</productname>. In this case you have to download the package <filename>bibletime-1.4-1.suse9.0.i586.rpm</filename>.
		Please download the package &quot;bibletime-i18n&quot; package, too. This package contains the available translations of the BibleTime user interface and handbook.
		</para>
		<para>If there are no packages for your version of Linux you have to install from source code. Please see below how to do that.
		</para>
	</section>

	<section><title>Installation from source code</title>
		<para>
		Installation using BibleTime's source code is more difficult than using binary packages. Please follow the steps below if you decided to install BibleTime from sources:

		<orderedlist>
			<listitem>
				<para>At first make sure the required software is installed on your system. Depending on your Linux distribution you have to install the development packages of the required software, too.
				</para>

				<itemizedlist>
					<listitem>
						<para><ulink url="http://www.kde.org/">KDE 3</ulink>.</para>
						<para>At least the libraries and the base package. KDE 3 is shipped with many Linux distributions. Very often it's installed by default.
						</para>
					</listitem>
<!--					<listitem>
						<para><ulink url="http://curl.sourceforge.net/">Curl >= 7.9</ulink>.</para>
						<para>This is necessary for the remote installation features of the new Sword Setup Dialog. Curl has to be installed before Sword.
						</para>
					</listitem>-->
					<listitem>
						<para><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/software/swordapi.jsp">Sword 1.5.8</ulink>.</para>
						<para>Installation instructions are available on <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/software/index.jsp">www.crosswire.org/sword/software</ulink>. Basically the installation steps are
							<screen>
								<command>./usrinst.sh --enable-shared --without-clucene</command>
								<command>make</command>
								<command>make install</command>
								<command>make install_config</command>
							</screen>
						</para>
					</listitem>
				</itemizedlist>

				<para>Please note that this list is only valid for the latest version of BibleTime, older versions may require other software.
				</para>
			</listitem>

			<listitem>
				<para>Compile and install BibleTime:
					<screen>
						<command>./configure --prefix=&lt;your KDE directory&gt;</command>
						<command>make</command>
						<command>make install</command>
					</screen>
				</para>

				<para>You can get your KDE directory by running the command <command>kde-config --prefix</command>. If you get problems please read our <olink targetdocent="software_faq">FAQ</olink>. If there's no solution of your problem, please contact us at <email>info@bibletime.info</email>.
				</para>
				
				<para>Debian (and possibly derived distros as well) use a non-standard path to
				store the documentation of KDE programs. Therefore the ./configure line above in
				this case needs to be changed to:
					<screen>
						<command>kde_htmldir=/usr/share/doc/kde/HTML ./configure --prefix=/usr</command>
					</screen>
				If you forget this, you'll likely not be able to access the handbook and the BibleStudy HowTo.
				</para>
			</listitem>
			
			<listitem>
				<para>Compile and install the translations of BibleTime's user interface (bibletime-i18n):
					<screen>
						<command>./configure --prefix=&lt;your KDE directory&gt;</command>
						<command>make</command>
						<command>make install</command>
					</screen>
				Please see the warning regarding nonstandard paths in the previous paragraph.
				</para>
			</listitem>

		</orderedlist>

		</para>
	</section>
</section>

<section><title>Install works</title>
	<para>
	You need Sword modules to work with BibleTime. Since version 1.4 BibleTime offers a userfriendly dialog (the Bookshelf Manager) to install/update/remove works. We strongly recommend this way to install works on your computer.
	</para>

	<para>
	Instructions for manual installation is available on <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/moduleinstall.jsp">www.crosswire.org/sword/modules</ulink>.
	</para>

	<section><title>Available types of works</title>
		<para>Here is a list of available types of works and where to get more information:
		</para>
		<para>
			<orderedlist>
				<listitem><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/ModDisp.jsp?modType=Bibles">Bibles</ulink></listitem>
				<listitem><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/ModDisp.jsp?modType=Commentaries">Commentaries</ulink></listitem>
				<listitem><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/ModDisp.jsp?modType=Dictionaries">Lexicons / Dictionaries</ulink></listitem>
				<listitem><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/ModDisp.jsp?modType=Books">Books</ulink></listitem>
			</orderedlist>
		</para>
	</section>

</section>

</webpage>
