<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
]>

<webpage id="documentation_ifaq">
<config param="desc" value="FAQ"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
<title>FAQ</title>
<summary>FAQ about BibleTime</summary>
<keywords>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, faq, questions, help</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
	<qandaset defaultlabel='number'>

		<qandadiv><title>Installation problems</title>
			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>Why is the toolbar missing?</para>
				</question>
				<answer>
					<para>
					Please run configure with the parameter --prefix=&lt;your KDE directory&gt;. Then run make and make install as usual.

					The KDE directories for the widely used Linux distributions are:
					<orderedlist>
						<listitem>RedHat: /usr</listitem>
						<listitem>SuSE: /opt/kde3</listitem>
						<listitem>Mandrake: /usr</listitem>
					</orderedlist>

					Alternatively you can run the command "kde-config --prefix" to get your KDE directory.
					The commands are:
					<orderedlist>
						<listitem>./configure --prefix=&lt;your KDE directory&gt;</listitem>
						<listitem>make</listitem>
						<listitem>make install</listitem>
					</orderedlist>
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>

			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>The translations are missing!</para>
				</question>
				<answer>
					<para>
					Please install the package bibletime-i18n which contains the translations of the daily tips, the handbook, the installation instructions and the Bible study howto.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>

		</qandadiv>

		<qandadiv><title>Usage problems</title>
			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>
					Is it possible to search for a specific Strong number?
					</para>
				</question>

				<answer>
					<para>
					You need at least BibleTime 1.1 for this. Turn on the default usage of Strong's numbers in the optionsdialog (Sword-&gt;Filter settings). Then open the seachdialog and search for &lt;0120&gt; or any other Strong code.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>

			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>
					Why do I see only question marks instead of Unicode text?
					</para>
				</question>

				<answer>
					<para>
					First make sure you have the latest version of the module which has the problems! Check <ulink url="www.crosswire.org/sword">www.crosswire.org/sword</ulink> for this.
					</para>
					<para>
					You have to install an unicode font like Code2000, Arial Unicode MS or Bitstream Cyberbit to display the special unicode characters. Check the section "Configuring BibleTime->Options Dialog->Fonts" in the handbook of BibleTime how to setup Unicode fonts under Linux.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>
		</qandadiv>

		<qandadiv><title>Modules</title>
			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>The KJV shows no Strongs numbers in the NT!</para>
				</question>

				<answer>
					<para>
					Due to copyright problems the old KJV module which contained all Strongs numbers had to be removed. The project KJV2003 was started to create a public domain text with all Strong numbers in it. At this time it's not yet finished so the numbers are not available in all verses of the NT. The status of the project is available at Crosswire.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>

			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>Where can I write down my personal notes?</para>
				</question>

				<answer>
					<para>
					You have to install the module "Personal", which is available as a commentary on <ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/modules/ModInfo.jsp?modName=Personal">Crosswire</ulink>. See our commentary page for more information: Commentaries.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>


			<qandaentry>
				<question>
					<para>Why is one of the two testaments of a Bible module empty?</para>
				</question>

				<answer>
					<para>
					Some modules only contain the text of the old or new testament. Recent versions of BibleTime should only offer the testament which has some text in it.
					</para>
				</answer>
			</qandaentry>

		</qandadiv>
	</qandaset>
</section>

</webpage>