<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
]>

<webpage id="software_about">
<config param="desc" value="Software page"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
	<title>About BibleTime</title>
	<summary>Introduction to the BibleTime software</summary>
	<keywords>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, about</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Introduction</title>
<para>
BibleTime is a Bible study program for Linux and is based on the K Desktop Environment (KDE).
</para>
</section>

<section><title>The history of BibleTime</title>
<para>
Back in June of 1999 Thomas Hagedorn, Thorsten Uhlmann and Joachim Ansorg started to work on a Bible study application for KDE 1.0.
</para>

<para>
The first version was released two months later as version 0.1. This version was very simple and supported only the most basic things.
</para>

<para>
After three months of hard work version 0.2 was released to the public. This version was usable, it supported basic printing, searching and offered a simple editor for personal notes.
</para>

<para>
BibleTime 0.2 was later ported to KDE 2 and totally redesigned with a more powerful interface, better printing and a lot of internal changes. This version was called BibleTime 0.3
</para>

<para>
BibleTime 1.0, which was released almost one year after version 0.3 and was the first version we considered as stable.
</para>

<para>
BibleTime 1.1 and 1.2 followed later on. BibleTime 1.2 is the first version of BibleTime for version 3.0 of KDE.
</para>
</section>

<section><title>The future of BibleTime</title>
<para>
We're grateful that God supports us and that He blesses our work with new team members. God is good!
</para>

<para>
We will continue our work, and as BibleTime improves we'll hopefully reach a point where BibleTime lacks only few things which are useful for a normal Bible study application.
</para>
</section>

</webpage>
