<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_about SYSTEM "software_about.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY software_download SYSTEM "software_download.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY documentation_requirements SYSTEM "documentation_requirements.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY documentation_installation_modules SYSTEM "documentation_installation_modules.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="documentation_installation_bibletime">
<config param="desc" value="Installation of the BibleTime software"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"/>
<head>
<title
>Sobre o BibleTime</title>
<summary
>Introduction to the BibleTime software</summary>
<keywords
>BibleTime, Software, Installation, Help, Sword, Download</keywords>
</head>

<section
><title
>Instalação do BibleTime</title>
<para
> Esta página explica como o BibleTime deve ser instalado. Por favor siga estes passos para ter uma instalação do BibleTime funcionando rápido. </para>

<section
><title
>As duas maneira de instalar o BibleTime</title>
	<para
> Existem duas possibilidades para instalar o BibleTime no seu sistema: <orderedlist
> <listitem
>Instalar usando pacotes binários pré-construídos, como RPM ou DEB</listitem
> <listitem
>Compilar o BibleTime usando os códigos fonte em seu sistema</listitem
> </orderedlist
> </para>

	<para
> Nós recomendamos a instalação usando os pacotes binários. É a maneira mais simples. </para>
</section>

<section
><title
>Pacotes binários pré-construídos</title>
	<para
> Nós tentamos fornecer pacotes para as distribuições Linux mais importantes. Isto inclui RedHat, Mandrake e SuSE. </para>

	<para
> First download the binary package for your Linux distribution. For example: You want to download BibleTime 1.2.2 for SuSE Linux 8.1. In this case you have to download the package &raquo;bibletime-1.2.2-1suse8.1.i586.rpm&laquo;. Please don't forgot to download the package bibletime-doc to get the documentation and the translations, which are available for BibleTime. </para>

	<para
> Como você pode ver cada nome de pacote contêm a distribuição Linux e versão para a qual foi construído. Por favor não tente instalar um pacote em outro sistema para o qual não foi construído. </para>

	<para
> You can download BibleTime here: <olink targetdocent="software_download"
>Download BibleTime</olink
>. Don't forget to install some text modules after you installed BibleTime: <olink targetdocent="documentation_installation_modules"
>How to install the text modules</olink
>. </para>
</section>


<section
><title
>Compilação do código fonte</title>
	<para
> Installation using BibleTime's source code is more difficult than using binary packages. Please follow the steps below if you decided to install BibleTime from sources: <orderedlist
> <listitem
> Install the required software: <olink targetdocent="documentation_requirements"
>BibleTime's requirements</olink
> </listitem
> <listitem
> Get the source code package of BibeTime: <olink targetdocent="software_download"
>Download</olink
> </listitem
> <listitem
> Compile and install BibleTime: <programlisting>
<![CDATA[
	./configure --prefix=<your KDE directory>
	make
 	make install
]]>
			</programlisting
> You can get your KDE directory by running the command <command
>kde-config --prefix</command
>. If you get problems please read the FAQ here: <olink targetdocent="documentation_faq"
>FAQ</olink
>. If there's no solution of your problem, please contact us at <email
>info@bibletime.info</email
> </listitem
> </orderedlist
> Don't forget to install some text modules after you installed BibleTime: <olink targetdocent="documentation_installation_modules"
>How to install the text modules</olink
>. </para>
</section>

</section>
</webpage>

