<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_intro_page SYSTEM "software_intro.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY development_join SYSTEM "development_join.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY translations SYSTEM "translation.xml" NDATA XML>
]>

<webpage id="development_help">
<config param="desc" value="Help us"
></config>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"
></config>
<head>
<title
>후원하기</title>
<summary
>Direct and indirect support for the development of BibleTime</summary>
<keywords
>BibleTime, Help us, Help BibleTime, Software</keywords>
</head>

<section
><title
>Please help us ...</title>
<para
>Our aim is to develop BibleTime into a really mature Bible study application that can by everyone. To ahieve this, we need your help. There are different possibilities for supporting the BibleTime project directly and indirectly: </para>

<section
><title
>기도해주시겠습니까?</title>
<para
>중보기도는 누구나가 동참할 수 있는 방법입니다. 당신께서 스워드(Sword)와 바이블타임 프로젝트를 위해 기도해주신다면, 당신은 프로젝트팀과 함께 사역하고 있는것입니다. </para>
</section>

<section
><title
>프로그래밍을 할 줄 아십니까?</title>
<para
>Do you know how to program in C++? Are you familiar with the KDE programming interface or are motivate to learn it? If you have time to regularly work on the BibleTime source code we ask you to join our team. If you want to do so, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join"
> Join us</olink
>. </para>
</section>

<section
><title
>문서 작성을 할 줄 아십니까?</title>
<para
>Do you think you would be good in working on BibleTime's english documentation? If you think you are, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join"
> Join us</olink
>. </para>
</section>

<section
><title
>영문 번역에 자신이 있으십니까?</title>
<para
>BibleTime should be useable for everyone. That's why we need a translation into your language, if it's not yet available. If you decide to start working on a translation please contact us at info@bibletime.info to see whether the translation was not yet started by another team member. We will provide you with the files which should be translated. </para>
<para
>You can find more information about the translation process on the page <olink targetdocent="translations"
> translation</olink
>. </para>
</section>
</section>

</webpage>
