<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
]>

<webpage id="translation">
<config param="desc" value="Software page"
></config>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date$"
></config>
<head>
	<title
>Traduction</title>
	<summary
>BibleTime translation statistics</summary>
	<keywords
>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, tramslation, webpage</keywords>
</head>

<section
><title
>Help translate BibleTime into your language</title>
<para
>This is a part of software development where the help of many individals is needed. It is our desire to offer BibleTime to users in as many languages as possible. The following areas are open for your contributions: <orderedlist numeration="arabic">
	<listitem
><para
>Translate the www.bibletime.info website.</para
></listitem>
	<listitem
><para
>Translate the program's User Interface.</para
></listitem>
	<listitem
><para
>Translate the program's handbook.</para
></listitem>
</orderedlist>
</para>

<para
>On this page you can find statistics about the completeness of existing translations for each of these areas, as well as links to translation templates that you can use to submit new translations which do not yet exist. If a translation into your language does not yet exist, just download the templates, translate them and send them to <email
>info@bibletime.info</email
>. If you are not satisfied with the status of your language's translation, you can directly download the corresponding file, update the translation and send it in. In both cases we'll be sure to integrate your work as soon as possible. </para>

<para
>For the translation process we recommend that you use the excellent and mature program <ulink url="http://i18n.kde.org/tools/kbabel/"
>KBabel</ulink
>. It has many advanced features and is a great aid. </para>
</section>


<section
><title
>Translate the www.bibletime.info website.</title>
<para
>If a translation of the website to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate the <ulink url="/en/pot/full.pot"
>Webpage translation template</ulink
>. If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to download the corresponding file. </para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/website_stats.pl"
></ssi>
</section>

<section
><title
>Translate the program's User Interface.</title>
<para
>If a translation of the User Interface to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate the <ulink url="http://cvs.sourceforge.net/viewcvs.py/*checkout*/bibletime/bibletime/pot/messages.pot?rev=HEAD"
> User Interface translation template</ulink
>. If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to download the corresponding file. </para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/messages_stats.pl"
></ssi>
</section>

<section
><title
>Translate the program's handbook.</title>
<para
>If a translation of the handbook to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate the <ulink url="http://cvs.sourceforge.net/viewcvs.py/*checkout*/bibletime/bibletime/pot/handbook.pot?rev=HEAD"
> handbook translation template</ulink
>. If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to download the corresponding file. </para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/handbook_stats.pl"
></ssi>
</section>

</webpage>
